// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which country won the first ever World Cup in 1930?",
    answer: "Uruguay",
    options: [
      "Brazil",
      "Germany",
      "Uruguay",
      "France"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Ronaldo is synonymous with the No.7, but what other number did he wear at Real Madrid?",
    answer: "9",
    options: [
      "8",
      "10",
      "11",
      "9"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which club is associated with 'Galacticos'?",
    answer: "Real Madrid",
    options: [
      "Real Madrid",
      "Barcelona",
      "River Plate",
      "Manchester City"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in the Premier League?",
    answer: "Sadio Mane",
    options: [
      "Sadio Mane",
      "Alan Sheara",
      "Andy Caroll",
      "Wayne Rooney"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Messi has won a record number of Ballon d'Or awards - how many?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "8",
      "5",
      "6",
      "7"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which city is home to two La Liga clubs?",
    answer: "Madrid",
    options: [
      "Seville",
      "Barcelona",
      "Madrid",
      "Bilbao"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Former Ballon d'Or winner Andriy Shevchenko is from which nation?",
    answer: "Ukraine",
    options: [
      "Belarus",
      "Russia",
      "Estonia",
      "Ukraine"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who won the man of the match award for the 2014 World Cup final?",
    answer: "Mario Götze",
    options: [
      "Mario Götze",
      "Sergio Romero",
      "Martín Demichelis",
      "Lionel Messi"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who was the first non-European to win the Ballon d'Or?",
    answer: "George Weah",
    options: [
      "Ronaldo",
      "Pelé",
      "Rivaldo",
      "George Weah"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What Is The Nickname Of Manchester United?",
    answer: "The Red Devils",
    options: [
      "The Red Lions",
      "The Gunners",
      "The Old Lady",
      "The Red Devils"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];